{"1":{"question":"\u00bfC\u00f3mo te llamas? ","answers":{"1":{"answer":"Juan","istrue":true},"2":{"answer":"Mart\u00edn ","istrue":false},"3":{"answer":"Jos\u00e9 ","istrue":false}}},"2":{"question":"Chala la? ","answers":{"1":{"answer":"Hj","istrue":true},"2":{"answer":"H","istrue":false},"3":{"answer":"H","istrue":false}}},"3":{"question":"Gh","answers":{"1":{"answer":"Jj","istrue":true},"2":{"answer":"Bjj","istrue":false},"3":{"answer":"Hjj","istrue":false}}},"4":{"question":"Hjj","answers":{"1":{"answer":"Hh","istrue":true},"2":{"answer":"Bbh","istrue":false},"3":{"answer":"Jj","istrue":false}}},"5":{"question":"Jjj","answers":{"1":{"answer":"Bhh","istrue":true},"2":{"answer":"Hh","istrue":false},"3":{"answer":"Hj","istrue":false}}},"6":{"question":"Hh","answers":{"1":{"answer":"Vbh","istrue":true},"2":{"answer":"G","istrue":false},"3":{"answer":"Hh","istrue":false}}},"7":{"question":"Hhj","answers":{"1":{"answer":"Hhh","istrue":true},"2":{"answer":"Hhh","istrue":false},"3":{"answer":"Cvv","istrue":false}}},"8":{"question":"Hhh","answers":{"1":{"answer":"Hh","istrue":true},"2":{"answer":"Hhh","istrue":false},"3":{"answer":"Hhh","istrue":false}}},"9":{"question":"Ghh","answers":{"1":{"answer":"Hhj","istrue":true},"2":{"answer":"Jjj","istrue":false},"3":{"answer":"Hhj","istrue":false}}},"10":{"question":"Hhh","answers":{"1":{"answer":"Hh","istrue":true},"2":{"answer":"Kj","istrue":false},"3":{"answer":"Bh","istrue":false}}},"11":{"question":"\u00bfQuiora ez? ","answers":{"1":{"answer":"Gg","istrue":true},"2":{"answer":"Hy","istrue":false},"3":{"answer":"Tg","istrue":false}}},"12":{"question":"Vvh","answers":{"1":{"answer":"Vgg","istrue":true},"2":{"answer":"Yju","istrue":false},"3":{"answer":"Vh","istrue":false}}},"13":{"question":"Hvh","answers":{"1":{"answer":"Vh","istrue":true},"2":{"answer":"Vb","istrue":false},"3":{"answer":"Bj","istrue":false}}},"14":{"question":"Ggg","answers":{"1":{"answer":"Hhh","istrue":true},"2":{"answer":"Vhh","istrue":false},"3":{"answer":"Cgg","istrue":false}}},"15":{"question":"\u00bfEsta final? ","answers":{"1":{"answer":"Bj","istrue":true},"2":{"answer":"Hh","istrue":false},"3":{"answer":"Jj","istrue":false}}}}